Oladayo Oladele

Customer Success Manager Saas

Port Harcourt patoladele@gmail.com +33 (0) 7 58 39 00 23

A bilingual professional with a zest for learning and self-development. I possess a blend of business and technical skills to contribute to the growth of organizations. 3+ years' experience in business development, sales and customer facing roles. Above all I am passionate about software development and new technologies.

Work Experience

Product Developer

Cryptoplayground - Remote January 2021 to December 2021

Empathy planning, User personas, UX design, Front-End development, usability testing, wireframing, prototyping of mobile and web interface

Customer Success Manager---->Country manager France

Radiant Melanin London - London August 2019 to November 2020

Tracked customer satisfaction, Educated customers on products, develop strategies for client retention, organized sales events, demand planning and logistics monitoring London-France, Budgeting, Business localization and translation services, identified opportunities for new product propositions, client data analysis, B2B and B2C sales, UX design, social media and communication, customer service, Monthly reporting, partnership and collaboration management

International Damage Recovery Consultant

Enterprise Holdings - Paris (75) July 2017 to February 2019

Summary:Customer advisory and training, client portfolio/account management, client and team member onboarding, sales and customer service

Drove consumer sales and provided customer service for one of America's car rental company at the Paris head office analysing, accelerating, advising and giving recommendations on over 100 portfolios weekly.

Liaising with other business stakeholders to be able to establish the right damage recovery approach for each customer.

Establishing and maintaining relationships with internal and external insurance brokers, clients and partners

Spearheading team stat report preparation to top management for sales and KPI tracking. Responsible for handling insurance claims, damage recovery files, customer contracts, repair invoices/accounts.

Coaching, supervising and preparation of training materials for new recruit.

Coordinated and planned new software improvements. Analyses of departmental work processes an clearly communication and collaborating with the IT team needs and specifications.

Restructuring of team processes to meet the new objectives and goals of the business.

Business Developer

Augmented Intelligence Institute IVS - Copenhagen, DK July 2016 to October 2016

Summary:Created innovative pricing strategies and CRM that helped satisfy present clients and keep track of potential customers

Collaboratively worked with the Senior management team to maximize opportunities and generate sales activity with clients and partners.

Researched on emerging markets and technology trends

Established relevant client profile and use case scenarios via analysis of current and potential clients

Generated systematic approaches to reach new clients in a chosen market.

Data extraction using Google analytics and social media platforms

Lead service pricing activity through analysis of competitors and established pricing range based on industry standards.

Key achievement: Creation of innovative pricing strategies and CRM that helped satisfy present and keep track of potential customers

IT Application Analyst

Port Harcourt Refining Company NIGERIA October 2014 to January 2015

Change management of risks associated with 4 main application servers

- # Analysis of staff IT skill set to aid custom made training materials
- # Analysis of departmental workflow to aid design of new automated systems.
- # Increased awareness of innovative ideas to top management.
- # Designed and developed a company-accessible prototype platform for task assigning and KPI Key achievement: Overall, stock taking was made effective and downtimes reduced. There was an increase in productivity of software interfacing by 45% and increase in transparency and IT department's KPIs by 40%.

Education

Bachelors - Computer Engineering in Computer Science

Covenant University - Ota July 2013 to September 2018

Masters International Business in Business international

Grenoble Ecole De Management - Grenoble (38)

January 2015 to September 2017

Skills

Microsoft Suite (10+ years)

- SQL (1 year)
- Project Management (2 years)
- Analytic problem solving (3 years)
- Business process development (2 years)
- Leadership and team management (3 years)
- Good communication skills
- stratégie commerciale (Less than 1 year)
- User Experience (UX)
- User Interface (UI)
- JavaScript
- HTML5
- Agile
- SaaS
- Java
- React (1 year)
- Linux (3 years)
- Figma (2 years)
- Cloud computing (1 year)
- UNIX (1 year)
- Bootstrap (2 years)
- Product development (2 years)

Languages

- French Fluent
- English Expert

Links

http://linkedin.com/in/oladeleoladayo

https://github.com/DidiVerte

Groups

Carregeo Environnement

August 2021 to Present

Group advocationg for environment change.

I give my time to the cause by helping with website widgets and content localization

Additional Information

EXTRA PROFESSIONAL ACTIVITIES

- Analysis of market trends and product innovation at ARIESPAK
- Fundraising, outsourcing of services and communication audits with partners/sponsors for Go-Karting company, SPEEDWAY KARTS
- Project management and outsourcing of branding services for metallurgy company, BLUEFINITY
- Served under the NATIONAL YOUTH SERVICE CORPS programme as a computer studies teacher in addition to working on community development projects and fund generation.